(Raj:)But if we're really gonna do
a double date,
than we have to go over
some ground rules about Emily.
(Howard:)Like when it turns out
she's made of rubber,
(Howard:)I don't say anything?
(Raj:)She's very real.
(Howard:)That's what it says on the box.
Right next to "dishwasher safe."
(Raj:)See? This is exactly
the kind cf thing
(Raj:)I'm worried about you
saying in front of her.
(Howard:)I promise I'll be
on my best behavior.
(Raj:)You better be. No jokes about
how close I am with my dog.
(Raj:)Or the truth about how close
I am with my dog.
(Howard:)You got it.
(Raj:)No jokes about
the year I took ballet.
(Howard:)You took ballet?
(Raj:)God, you never listen.
(Leonard:)Are you sure you
want to do this?
(Sheldon:)The magazine articles suggest
that one of the ways
(Sheldon:)to get over a breakup
is a new look.
(Leonard:)What about your old look,
well-groomed ventriloquist doll?
-"Oh, my God, I do look like that."
-Stop it!